BENJAMIN STUART

Booval 4304 · 0475 701 823 Benjamin.Stuart001@outlook.com

I am a professional and driven radio operator and event staffer with a demonstrated history of working in large scale venues such as the Gabba and Suncorp stadium. With more than 3 years' experience in communications, I am skilled in secure radio operations, conflict resolution and fast paced work environments.

EXPERIENCE

OCTOBER 2018 - CURRENT

EVENT STAFFER & RADIO OPERATOR, CAP SECURITY SERVICES

- Communicate with staff via telecommunications to coordinate staff and vehicles movements
- Assist both QPS and QAS and, respond to forever changing security needs
- Assist and support hundreds of patrons throughout the working event
- Liaise with staff and clients regarding security needs
- Maintain a sanitary and tidy workplace
- Write accurate and concise reports of incidents and events and
- Provide heartwarming service to our patrons and customers

NOVEMBER 2019 – OCTOBER 2021

BOH 2IC, RASHAYS IPSWICH

- Manage kitchen staff and coordinate food orders
- Coordinate and maintain a food safe working environment
- Manage the hiring and training of BOH staff
- Manage and coordinate an accurate weekly stock take
- Hold meetings with BOH staff to address issues and ensure customer standards are met,
- Schedule kitchen staff shifts
- Order food supplies and kitchen equipment, as needed
- Ensure that food plating as well as portion sizes are correct and
- Detail clean and training others to detail clean broilers, fridges and dishwashers among other commercial equipment

JUNE 2016 - JUNE 2019

VOLUNTEER, AUSTRALIAN RED CROSS

- Trained and assisted staff in red cross retail operations
- Assisted in visual merchandising and promotions
- Clean and assist in general maintenance and
- Provide high level customer service, so that all customers are treated in a respectful, supportive and professional manner

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

IPSWICH STATE HIGH SCHOOL

• Queensland certificate of education.

2016 - 2018

THE UNIVERSITY OF QUEENSLAND

• Studied engineering for two years.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Strong time management
- Strong work ethic
- Customer service orientated
- Skilled in conflict resolution strategies
- Motivated, adaptable and flexible
- Problem solver
- Confident working solitary or in a team environment

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- Cooking
- Martial Arts
- Mathematics

- Software and Coding
- Video games

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

- Volunteered and raised funds for the Australian Red Cross for 2+ years.
- Acted and assisted in the development of 3 theater productions as a part of the ISHS drama club,
- Marched with Open Doors Youths Services during pride to raise awareness about mental health and equality.

REFERENCES

RASHAYS IPSWICH
JAMIE LORD
RESTAURANT MANAGER
+61 497 843 814

CAP SECURITY SERVICES

KATHRYN PEARSON

CAP SECURITY SERVICES SUPERVISOR
+61 416 261 992